hey guys so last week I uh put a poll on
my blog uh asking a bunch of questions
and so this video is going to showcase
the results of that poll so first of all
thank you very very very much for
everyone who took the survey I learned a
lot and this stuff is great for me to
learn because uh you know had I not
asked these questions I wouldn't have
know the answer so um as you can see I
have the results uh up here on the blog
so here is the first question what is
your
gender um
so 952 + 791 this is uh so like around
1,750 people took took this
poll really sucks because last uh poll I
I I did the week before I had the like
3,000 over
3,100
responders but the uh the data the data
didn't work so I had to redo the poll
and I got uh you know probably around
60% of as many people answered this one
but oh well this is still a lot of
people so thanks to everyone who
answered as you can see it looks like I
have more male readers than female uh
around 55% of my readers are male and
45% are female the last poll I did it
was a more equal um a little bit more
equal but I was on embedding glute
pictures into my blog so I think more
women felt like responding to that one
so but at the very least this goes to
show you I have a lot of I have a very
high female readership I bet you a lot
of my colleagues have way more males
that read their blog than
females okay next question uh is what is
your
background about 8% of people are
strength coaches 21% are personal
trainers
uh around 6% are physical therapists or
athletic
trainers um 4% are exercise science
students and 62% of my readers are just
lifters looking to get results so the
vast majority are are just people who
lift weights and then around 21% are
personal trainers so that's very good
information to know okay the next
question what is your primary training
goal and this is what I thought it would
be um
41% of readers are reading my blog uh
with the goal of improving of learning
information to help them improve their
physique so the vast majority of people
are just trying to improve their
physique uh
27% their number one training goal is
strength uh 19% is their health and then
14% is improved Sports Performance so
this is uh good to know and that's
that's the order that I thought it would
be in so most people just want their
physique to look better uh followed by
strength health and then Sports
Performance next question how many years
have you been lifting weights this was
very surprising to me because uh the
lowest category was less than one year
11% of people have been Lifting for less
than a year 22% from 1 to 3 years uh
177% for 3 to 5 years 18% from 5 to 10
years and 33% of my readers have been
lifting weights for 10 or more years so
that that's crazy most of my readers the
uh the biggest category in my readership
has been Lifting for 10 or more years so
I've got a very uh
experienced uh readership uh we've been
lifting weights a lot of years that's
awesome all right next question how many
days uh do you lift weights per week and
this is what I would have expected so so
you've got at the at the very ends
you've got only
1% uh of lifters training one day a week
and 1% training seven times a week 9%
training 2 days a week and 6% training
six times a week and then the majority
is in the middle so you've got 15%
training five times a
week uh 35% training 3 days a week and
33% training four times a week so most
of the people fall in the middle here so
you've got 35 and 33 what is that 68% of
people train either three or four times
a week which is awesome
um I think it's ideal for me I think
three to three to six is ideal depending
on how you work it but uh that's great
to see that most people are training you
know three or more days a week that's
great okay what what type of training
split do you usually stick to um
the last when when I did the
the the last um poll that I did it it
was I thought that it said that most
people were doing a body part split
which confused me I wouldn't have
thought that so the last poll the the
the the pie charts were all screwy so
they weren't accurate um which is good
to see I wanted to redo it and get
actual data and actual numbers so this
was cool only 18% do body part splits
44% do full body routine
29% do lower upper splits and 9% do push
P so the the the bulk of my readership
does full body training followed by
lower upper splits followed by body part
splits followed by Push Pull and that's
what what I would have
expected all right what is your favorite
exercise uh I thought it was going to be
the squat it was not the squat it was
actually the deadlift 31% of people
liked the deadlift the second most
popular exercise or most favorite
exercise is the squat at
23% and then the next most popular
exercise was the hip thrust at
11% and then all these other
lifts uh were like couple in here got 5%
the chin up was five 5% shows the chin
up 5% shows the cell swing and
everything else was between 1 and
3% uh so that's very cool so my lifters
are very lower body dominant which is
great so uh again deadlifts got number
one squats number two hip thrust number
three for the favorite
exercise all right next question what
which exercise do you feel is the most
dangerous for
you
uh so this one uh was this one was very
telling the deadlift most dangerous it's
the most favorite exercise and also the
most dangerous exercise 30% of people
chose the deadlift 22% chose the the
squat uh 133% chose the bench press 13%
chose the military press only 5% chose
the Ben overo 16% chose the good morning
and only 1% chose the hip thrust so it
looks like the hip thrust is the safest
out of these uh out of these
exercises with the deadlift being the
most dangerous all right what is your
favorite glute
exercise 40% chose the hip thrust n 19%
chose the barbell glut bridge and 3%
chose the single leg hip thrust so it's
kind of interesting here between hip
thrust and Bridge
variations this adds up to
uh 62% of people chose a hip thrust
variation pretty interesting there
um next in line went uh the Bulgarian
split squat with
8% then it went the deadlift with 7%
then it went the
um sorry squat was 8% deadlift was 7%
and then Bulgarian split squat was
6% followed by uh the others here looks
like Kell swing went next and then uh
single leg
RDL and then lunge and then back
extension and then sled push and then
pistol um so this is great information
so 699 people voted for the hip thrust
the next was the Barbo glute Bridge
321 after that was the squat with 144
votes then the deadlift with 129 votes
then 103 votes for the Bulgarian split
squat okay which glute exercise do you
feel produces the most tension and
highest activation in your glutes in
this one the overwhelming winner was the
hip thrust 44% of people chose the hip
thrust
uh at 761 votes the next next highest
was 19% with the barbell glute Bridge
323 voters then it was the single leg
hip thrust with 148 votes got 9
9% and then it looks like the deadlift
was
next uh actually no the squat was
next then the Bulgarian split
squat then the deadlift
then uh the back ex then back extensions
and
lunges and uh pistols and kall swings so
very cool information here so the Bri
Bridges and and
thrusts uh again Trump everything for
tension and
activation all right next answer next
question is which glute exercise do you
feel produces the biggest pump and burn
and metabolic stress in your glutes uh
hip thrust one here it got 596 votes so
35% glute Bridge was next with 303 votes
at
18% and then uh next was the lateral
bandw walks which got 7% of votes at 113
votes and after that was 109 votes for
the single leg hip thrust at
6% then we've got looks like uh
deadlifts were
next followed by uh back
extensions followed by kle Bell
swings um oh Bulgarian split squats
actually were up there so good good to
see
here these my readers know how to get a
glute pump and uh looks like bridging
hip thrust and BR and glute Bridges came
out
Superior okay this was an interesting
question here which glute exercise do
you feel makes your glutes the sorest
and creates the most muscle damage in
the glutes I would have predicted that
the lunge would have won or the
Bulgarian split squat but um I feel my
glutes most with lunges second with
Bulgarian split squats in terms of being
sore the following
days but uh if we can see down here the
hip thrust actually won with this too so
the hip thrust swept every category for
glutes and I don't feel a lot of glute
damage the next day following with hip
thrust but this shows you that a lot of
people do and I've heard from people
I've heard a lot of people say my glutes
get so sore from hip thrust mine don't
but uh this goes to show you we all
function differently 371 votes for the
hip thrust
22% uh followed by the lunge with 367
votes also
22% and Then followed by the Bulgarian
split squat 246 votes at uh 14% %
followed by the
squat uh with with 144 votes
8% looks like uh next was the single leg
hip thrust 130 votes 8% and then a tie
for deadlifts and barbell glute Bridges
with 123 votes
7% and then uh looks like let's see sled
pushes got 47 votes what's nice is that
the the sled pushes aren't going to
create a lot of damage cuz they don't
have an Ecentric component so only 3% of
people voted for sled pushes
um anyway that was that was interesting
to me that was probably the most
interesting that I wouldn't have
predicted all that and then the last
question is what do you like most about
my site and this one was interesting to
me because uh most people the majority
48% like General strength training
info and then 67 votes or 35% for glute
info and then the least 303 votes or
177% for technical Sport Science info
so um to recap looks like my readers are
most interested in general strength
training uh with secondary preference
glute information and then technical
Sport
Science um the hip thrust followed by
the lung was the most damaging exercise
for the glutes the biggest burn was the
hip dust followed by the glute
Bridge most tension activation hip
thrust followed by glute Bridge favorite
glute exercise hip thrust followed by
glute Bridge most dangerous was the
deadlift followed by the
squat favorite exercise was the deadlift
followed by the
squat uh what Ty of training split full
body one beat beat out all the other
splits most people lift three or 4 days
a
week my readership has the most of most
of my readership H is in in the 10 or
more year category which is crazy the
majority of people well not the majority
but the the category that beat out all
the others for primary training goal was
physique and
Aesthetics most people who read my blog
are just lifters looking to get results
followed by personal trainers and I've
got a little bit more males reading my
site than
females okay that wraps it up thank you
very much for watching and thank you
very much for taking the poll